Neslihan Atasever

Frontend Developer

neslihan.ataseverr@gmail.com • 543 457 91 13

Düzce • Linkedin • Twitter • GitHub

Profile

My name is Neslihan, and I am a driven individual with a focus on personal and professional growth. I have a strong interest in web development. I am committed to continuous learning and improvement in my field. I'm a team-oriented person with excellent communication and collaboration skills, and have experience in project management and leadership. I am confident in my abilities and take a proactive approach to my work. I am also a hardworking and dedicated individual, who is committed to delivering high-quality results in all of my endeavors.

Skills

HTML | CSS | SASS | JavaScript | TypeScript

Angular | Flutter | Dart | Git | VueJs

Education

Management Information Systems,

Anadolu University Oct 2021 – Dec 2023 | Eskişehir, Turkey

Computer Programming, Sakarya University

Sep 2019 – Sep 2021 | Sakarya, Turkey

Organizations

Frontendship, Community Member Sep 2022 | Turkey

Youth Center Volunteer, Volunteer

May 2015 | Duzce, Turkey

Languages

Turkish (Native) | English (A2)

Certificates

Master Trainer | Young Leader | Team Leader

Project Development

References

Eray Gundogmus, *Sr. Frontend Developer*, Teknasyon gundogmuseray@gmail.com

Alican Gol, *Software Engineer*, Microsoft sahaf91@hotmail.com

Professional Experience

Frontend Developer, Designble

Dec 2022 | Istanbul, Turkey

I successfully made the Designble website responsive, designing pages for the About, Communication, Services, and other sections. Additionally, I resolved any errors on existing pages and fulfilled all necessary requests for the Designble site. While working on tasks received through Designble.net, I used Vanilla JS and SASS.

Frontend Developer, Atasayar Technology

Mar 2022 – Dec 2022 | Düzce, Turkey

As a web developer, I have experience with a range of technologies including HTML, CSS, TypeScript, and Angular. I have developed pages using Angular, and have contributed to the development of a company management panel, including implementing a project module for tracking and managing projects. I have also gained experience with the Dart programming language and Flutter framework, and am currently working on developing a mobile application.

I have utilized tools such as GitHub and Agile Board (YouTrack) for project management and collaboration, and have written maintenance contracts using HTML and CSS. I have continually sought to improve my skills through coursework in Angular, JavaScript, and Flutter. In my spare time, I am actively working on furthering my understanding of JavaScript and Angular.

Software Intern, Open Software

Sep 2020 – Dec 2020 | Düzce, Turkey

As a web developer, I have experience with HTML and CSS, and have used these technologies to create designs. I have also participated in code review and contributed to the development of small automations. These skills and experiences have allowed me to effectively contribute to web development projects and help ensure the quality and efficiency of the codebase.

Software Intern, Quantum Technology

May 2020 – Aug 2020 | Düzce, Turkey

We developed an automation using the C# language. I learned SQL for a while and worked as a Database administrator.

Content Author, Freelance

Apr 2017 – Apr 2019 | Düzce, Turkey I have produced SEO compatible content for many topics.

Software Intern, SEDAŞ

May 2018 – May 2019 | Düzce, Turkey I learned computer parts and helped with computer repairs.